loot.com 2009-10-17

# Loot.com - Classified Ads. Buy, rent or place a free ad to sell anything.

## [Search by category](http://www.loot.com/all-categories)

  * ### [Motoring](http://www.loot.com/motoring "Cars, motorbikes, scooters, vans, car hire, caravans, motorhomes, spares, accessories, insurance, finance, number plates and trailers.")

    *     * , [Car Accessories](http://www.loot.com/motoring/car-accessories-and-spares "Click here to search for Car Accessories")
    *     * , [Motorbikes](http://www.loot.com/motoring/bike "Click here to search for Motorbikes")
    *     * , [Motorbike Accessories](http://www.loot.com/motoring/motorbike-accessories-and-spares "Click here to search for Motorbike Accessories")
    *     * , [Commercial Vehicles](http://www.loot.com/motoring/commercial-vehicles--accessories-and-spares "Click here to search for Commercial Vehicles")
    *     * , [Mopeds and Scooters](http://www.loot.com/motoring/mopeds-and-scooters "Click here to search for Mopeds and Scooters")
    *     * , [Number Plates](http://www.loot.com/motoring/number-plates "Click here to search for Number Plates")
    *     * , [Caravans and Accessories](http://www.loot.com/motoring/caravans-and-accessories "Click here to search for Caravans and Accessories")
    *     * , [Car Audio](http://www.loot.com/motoring/car-audio-and-security "Click here to search for Car Audio")
    *     * , [Camper Vans](http://www.loot.com/motoring/camper-vans "Click here to search for Camper Vans")
    * …
  * ### [Property](http://www.loot.com/property "Flats, bedsits, houses, apartments, rooms, student accommodation, shares, house mates, buy, sell, let and more.")

    *     * , [Flat/House Shares](http://www.loot.com/rs6/cl.asp?ss_id=&action=fsrlt&pn=&cc=&ad_id=&atp=property&ps=undefined&cpg=sf&ord=&iss=&prc=&ukloc=&c1=11076&c2=&subtap=share_lvl2&psc=&kyd=&psc_dis=&mnp=&mxp=&adroomtype=&do=&pt= "Click here to search for Flat/House Shares")
    *     * , [Garages](http://www.loot.com/property/garaging "Click here to search for Garages")
    *     * , [Houses to Rent](http://www.loot.com/rs6/cl.asp?ss_id=&action=fsrlt&pn=&cc=&ad_id=&atp=property&ps=undefined&cpg=sf&ord=&iss=&prc=&ukloc=&c1=11072&c2=&subtap=rent_lvl2&psc=&kyd=house&psc_dis=&mnp=&mxp=&adbedrooms=&do=&hstype= "Click here to search for Houses to Rent")
    *     * , [Flats to Buy](http://www.loot.com/rs6/cl.asp?ss_id=&action=fsrlt&pn=&cc=&ad_id=&atp=property&ps=undefined&cpg=sf&ord=&iss=&prc=&ukloc=&c1=11075&c2=&subtap=buy_lvl2&psc=&kyd=flat&psc_dis=&mnp=&mxp=&hstype=&adbedrooms=&do= "Click here to search for Flats to Buy")
    *     * , [Property Abroad](http://www.loot.com/property/property-abroad "Click here to search for Property Abroad")
    *     * , [Houses to Buy](http://www.loot.com/rs6/cl.asp?ss_id=&action=fsrlt&pn=&cc=&ad_id=&atp=property&ps=undefined&cpg=sf&ord=&iss=&prc=&ukloc=&c1=11075&c2=&subtap=buy_lvl2&psc=&kyd=house&psc_dis=&mnp=&mxp=&hstype=&adbedrooms=&do= "Click here to search for Houses to Buy")
    *     * , [Student Accomodation](http://www.loot.com/property/student-accommodation "Click here to search for Student Accomodation")
    *     * , [Property Abroad](http://www.loot.com/property/property-abroad "Click here to search for Property Abroad")
    *     * , [Houseboats](http://www.loot.com/property/houseboats "Click here to search for Houseboats")
    *     * , [Bedsits](http://www.loot.com/rs6/cl.asp?ss_id=&action=fsrlt&atp=property&ps=undefined&cpg=sf&kyp=&subtap=ap_lvl2&ord=&prc=&kyd=bedsit&c1=11074 "Click here to search for Bedsits")
    * …
  * ### [Home & Garden](http://www.loot.com/home-garden "Bathroom furniture, bedroom furniture, DIY, carpets and rugs, cookers, fridges, dishwashers, microwaves, gardening, pets, clothes...")

    *     * , [Garden Furniture](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/garden-furniture-and-sheds "Click here to search for Garden Furniture")
    *     * , [Watches](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/watches-and-jewellery "Click here to search for Watches")
    *     * , [Baby Items](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/childrens-and-baby-items "Click here to search for Baby Items")
    *     * , [Dogs](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/dogs "Click here to search for Dogs")
    *     * , [Antiques](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/antiques "Click here to search for Antiques")
    *     * , [Furniture](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/furniture "Click here to search for Furniture")
    *     * , [Fires and Heating](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/fires-and-heating "Click here to search for Fires and Heating")
    *     * , [Toys and Games](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/toys-and-games "Click here to search for Toys and Games")
    *     * , [Kitchen Accessories](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/kitchen-accessories "Click here to search for Kitchen Accessories")
    *     * , [House Clearances](http://www.loot.com/home-garden/house-clearances "Click here to search for House Clearances")
    * …
  * ### [Electrical](http://www.loot.com/electrical "Computers, DVD players, hi-fi, laptops, mobile phones, TVs, camcorders and more.")

    *     * , [Computer Parts](http://www.loot.com/electrical/computer-parts-and-accessories "Click here to search for Computer Parts")
    *     * , [PCs](http://www.loot.com/electrical/personal-and-business-computers "Click here to search for PCs")
    *     * , [TVs](http://www.loot.com/electrical/televisions "Click here to search for TVs")
    *     * , [Games Consoles](http://www.loot.com/electrical/consoles-and-computer-games "Click here to search for Games Consoles")
    *     * , [Laptop and PDAs](http://www.loot.com/electrical/laptop-and-handheld-computers "Click here to search for Laptop and PDAs")
    *     * , [DVDs](http://www.loot.com/electrical/dvd-and-video-films "Click here to search for DVDs")
    *     * , [Cameras](http://www.loot.com/electrical/cameras-and-accessories "Click here to search for Cameras")
    *     * , [Hi-Fi](http://www.loot.com/electrical/hi-fi "Click here to search for Hi-Fi")
    *     * , [Fridges and Freezers](http://www.loot.com/electrical/fridges-and-freezers "Click here to search for Fridges and Freezers")
    *     * , [Cookers](http://www.loot.com/electrical/cookers--hobs-and-microwaves "Click here to search for Cookers")
    *     * , [Vacuum Cleaners](http://www.loot.com/electrical/vacuum-cleaners "Click here to search for Vacuum Cleaners")
    * …
  * ### [Music](http://www.loot.com/music "Drums, guitars, gigs, DJ equipment, karaoke, saxophones, amps and more.")

    *     * , [Drums and Percussion](http://www.loot.com/music/drums-and-percussion- "Click here to search for Drums and Percussion")
    *     * , [CDs](http://www.loot.com/music/cds--records-and-tapes "Click here to search for CDs")
    *     * , [String Instruments](http://www.loot.com/music/string-instruments "Click here to search for String Instruments")
    *     * , [Karaoke Equipment](http://www.loot.com/music/karaoke-and-disco-equipment "Click here to search for Karaoke Equipment")
    *     * , [Pianos and Keyboards](http://www.loot.com/music/pianos--keyboards-and-organs "Click here to search for Pianos and Keyboards")
    *     * , [Noticeboard](http://www.loot.com/music/musicians-noticeboard "Click here to search for Noticeboard")
    *     * , [Studio and Band Equipment](http://www.loot.com/music/studio-and-band-equipment "Click here to search for Studio and Band Equipment")
    *     * , [Guitars](http://www.loot.com/music/guitars "Click here to search for Guitars")
    * …
  * ### [Leisure](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests "Antiques, art & craft, astrology, books, digital cameras, football, cricket, golf, gym equipment, fishing, snooker and pool.")

    *     * , [Collectibles](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/collectibles-and-collections "Click here to search for Collectibles")
    *     * , [Football](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/football "Click here to search for Football")
    *     * , [Gym Equipment](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/gym-and-fitness-equipment "Click here to search for Gym Equipment")
    *     * , [Health Beauty](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/health-and-beauty-services "Click here to search for Health Beauty")
    *     * , [Golf](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/golf "Click here to search for Golf")
    *     * , [Bicycles](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/bicycles--accessories-and-spares "Click here to search for Bicycles")
    *     * , [Fishing](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/fishing "Click here to search for Fishing")
    *     * , [Knitting and Sewing](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/knitting-and-sewing "Click here to search for Knitting and Sewing")
    *     * , [Camping Equipment](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/camping-equipment "Click here to search for Camping Equipment")
    *     * , [Arts and Crafts](http://www.loot.com/hobbies-interests/art-and-craft-materials "Click here to search for Arts and Crafts")
    * …
  * ### [Dating](http://www.loot.com/dating "Love, friendship, dating and introduction agencies.")

    *     * , [Dating Agencies](http://www.dating.loot.com/ "Click here to search for Dating Agencies")
    *     * , [Women Seeking Men](http://www.dating.loot.com/ "Click here to search for Women Seeking Men")
    *     * , [Men Seeking Men](http://www.dating.loot.com/ "Click here to search for Men Seeking Men")
    *     * , [Women Seeking Women](http://www.dating.loot.com/ "Click here to search for Women Seeking Women")
    *     * , [Friendship UK](http://www.dating.loot.com/ "Click here to search for Friendship UK")
    * …
  * ### [What's On](http://www.loot.com/whats-on "Auctions, car boot sales, tickets, concerts and events.")

    *     * , [Lost](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/lost "Click here to search for Lost")
    *     * , [Penpals](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/penpals "Click here to search for Penpals")
    *     * , [Tickets](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/tickets "Click here to search for Tickets")
    *     * , [Auctions](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/auctions "Click here to search for Auctions")
    *     * , [What's On](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/whats-on "Click here to search for What's On")
    *     * , [Swap Shop](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/swap-shop "Click here to search for Swap Shop")
    *     * , [Vouchers](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/vouchers "Click here to search for Vouchers")
    *     * , [Public and Legal Notices](http://www.loot.com/whats-on/public-and-legal-notices "Click here to search for Public and Legal Notices")
    * …
  * ### [Travel](http://www.loot.com/travel "Holidays abroad, holidays throughout the UK, hotels, guest houses, Bed & breakfast, working holidays, insurance and flights.")

    *     * , [Holidays in Europe](http://www.loot.com/travel/holidays-in-europe "Click here to search for Holidays in Europe")
    *     * , [Holidays in Spain](http://www.loot.com/travel/holidays-in-spain "Click here to search for Holidays in Spain")
    *     * , [Holidays in USA/Florida](http://www.loot.com/travel/holidays-in-usa-florida "Click here to search for Holidays in USA/Florida")
    *     * , [Holidays in Wales](http://www.loot.com/travel/holidays-in-wales "Click here to search for Holidays in Wales")
    *     * , [Travel Tickets](http://www.loot.com/travel/travel-tickets "Click here to search for Travel Tickets")
    * …
  * ### [Business & Loans](http://www.loot.com/business "Business opportunities, business services, financial services, loans, office equipment, office furniture and virtual office.")

    *     * , [Office Furniture](http://www.loot.com/business/office-furniture "Click here to search for Office Furniture")
    *     * , [Air Conditioners](http://www.loot.com/business/air-conditioners-and-dehumidifiers "Click here to search for Air Conditioners")
    *     * , [Business Opportunities](http://www.loot.com/business/business-opportunities "Click here to search for Business Opportunities")
    *     * , [Industrial Machinery](http://www.loot.com/business/office-furniture "Click here to search for Industrial Machinery")
    *     * , [Businesses for Sale](http://www.loot.com/business/businesses-for-sale "Click here to search for Businesses for Sale")
    * …
  * ### [Event Tickets](http://www.loot.com/tickets "Find deals on tickets for gigs, concerts and shows")

    *     * , [Sports](http://www.loot.com/tickets/sports "Click here to search for Sports Tickets")
    *     * , [Theatre and Arts](http://www.loot.com/tickets/theatreandarts "Click here to search for Theatre and Arts Tickets")
    * …
  * ### [Jobs & Training](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/ "Permanent roles, temporary jobs, contracts - sales, marketing, administration, professional and trade.")

    *     * , [Health](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=OT "Click here to search for Health Jobs")
    *     * , [Construction](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=CN "Click here to search for Construction Jobs")
    *     * , [IT](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=IT "Click here to search for IT Jobs")
    *     * , [Travel and Hospitality](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=TV "Click here to search for Travel and Hospitality Jobs")
    *     * , [Customer Services](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=CU "Click here to search for Customer Services Jobs")
    *     * , [Office and Administration](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=SE "Click here to search for Office and Administration Jobs")
    *     * , [Sales](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=SM "Click here to search for Sales Jobs")
    *     * , [Retail](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=RT "Click here to search for Retail Jobs")
    *     * , [Banking and Finance](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=FI "Click here to search for Banking and Finance Jobs")
    *     * , [Marketing](http://loot.jobex.co.uk/cgi-bin/advsearch?search_emp_mkt_cd=MK "Click here to search for Marketing Jobs")
    * …
  * ### [Competitions](http://competitions.loot.com/ "Start Winning Prizes Now!")

  * ### [Astrology](http://loot.forturi.com/app/page/homepage)

| 

## Data Protection and Privacy Policy

We are Loot Limited, (Company registration number 4281775, data protection registered number Z6419373) ("Loot/we/us").

Loot Ltd is part of the Daily Mail & General Trust (DMGT) group. At Loot Ltd and our associated companies, we take your privacy seriously. Please be assured that we will safeguard any information that you provide and will never release your personal details to other companies without your express permission.

This privacy policy explains how Loot may collect information from you via our website and how that information may be used subsequently. If you have any queries in relation to this privacy policy please contact [legal@lootmail.com](mailto:legal@lootmail.com).

By browsing and using our website you agree to this policy governing your use of the website. If you do not accept this policy, you must not use our website.

This policy applies only to this website and not to other websites to which we provide links. We also enter into agreements with commercial partners whose websites may be co-branded or framed by us and which you may visit directly through our website. These websites are not subject to our privacy policy. You are advised to read the privacy policy of such other websites.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time without notification and you should regularly review this policy when you visit our site.

## Collection of information

In order to provide the services you want, and to allow you to experience a more personalised service when you revisit us, we need to know your interests. We find these out by asking you, by reading your comments and by looking at which are the most popular areas of our sites.

## Collection of personal information

We would like to use your registered details to contact you with relevant offers and services. We will only collect personal information from you (such as name, address, telephone number, email address etc) which you have provided voluntarily to us either by completing registration or enquiry forms or sending emails to us. Please do not submit your personal data to us if you do not wish us to collect it.

## When you register with Loot we may ask for the following details:

  * Your e-mail address
  * Your password
  * Your title
  * Your name
  * Your postcode
  * Your home/work telephone number
  * Your mobile telephone number
  * Your street/flat number
  * The region of the UK in which you live

Most of this information is entered into Loot's customer database (we do not keep details of your password).

Further examples of where we may collect your personal information include (without limitation):-

  * If you order a product or service from us we may ask for information including your name, e-mail address, delivery and billing address, credit or debit card number and expiry date. Sometimes we may ask for your telephone number to be forwarded to the couriers who may deliver your order. These details allow us to process your orders efficiently.  

  * If you enter a contest or promotion we ask for your name, address and e-mail address. This is so we can run the contest effectively and tell you if you have won.

## Collection of other information

In addition to asking you to submit personal information, we may collect information about you automatically when you visit the site. The collection of information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. A web beacon is a small graphic image placed on a web page that is designed to allow us to monitor visitors to our site. A cookie is small text file that is placed on your computer's hard drive by your web browser when you first visit our site. The cookie allows us to identify your computer and find out details about your last visit. Most internet browsers accept cookies automatically, but usually you can alter the settings of your browser to erase cookies or prevent automatic acceptance if you prefer. If you choose not to receive our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience with our website will be as quick or responsive as if you do receive cookies.

 The information collected by cookies and web beacons is not personally identifiable, it includes general information about your computer settings, your connection to the internet e.g. operating system and platforms, IP address, your browsing patterns and timings of browsing on our website and your geographical location.

## Use of your information

You agree that we may obtain, hold, correlate, merge and use your information (including personal information) for the purpose of providing you with our services and ancillary services and for our internal business purposes. These include (without limitation):-

  * personalising your visits to the site and developing the design and style of the site to improve our services to you;
  * to inform you about the latest changes to our website, or products, services or promotional offers that you might find interesting;
  * communication (and personalising such communication) with you from Loot, from other Daily Mail & General Trust ('DMGT') group companies and from other reputable and trustworthy third parties (if you have agreed to such);
  * informing you if you have been successful in any of the competitions or promotions;
  * compiling customer reviews;
  * for market research purposes;
  * to prevent you from posting illegal, offensive or objectionable comments on our sites;
  * to enable third parties to carry out statistical analysis, technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf including determining behavioural preferences to manage online advertising;
  * for strategic development;
  * for any purpose required by law or regulation; and
  * for accounting purposes.

##  Sharing Information

We may disclose your information to any company within the DMGT group of companies by means of a centralised database to which all companies have access or by means of a direct transfer of data from one office to another.

We may provide third parties, at our discretion, with certain aggregate statistical data about your use of our websites, which data may include demographic data such as age range and/or geographic location of groups of user. It will not include information that could personally identify you.

With your consent, we may supply personal information to third parties.

We reserve the right to access and to disclose personal information to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests or requests by applicable regulatory bodies, to operate our systems properly or to protect either ourselves or our other users.

We may transfer, sell or assign any of the information described in this policy to third parties as a result of a sale, merger, consolidation, change of control, transfer of assets or reorganisation of Loot.

You consent to the transfer of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area (which may not provide the same protection for such information as the United Kingdom provides) in the event that the processing of your information involves such a transfer

## Monitoring emails

We may monitor and keep records of email communications which you send to us and other communications with you in accordance with this policy and our other business interests.

## Safeguards and Security

No data transmission over the internet can be entirely secure, and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information and/or use of our sites. However we use our reasonable endeavours to protect the security of your personal information from unauthorised access or use by using Secure Sockets Layer 128-bit encryption.

## Credit Card

Loot takes great care to ensure your credit card information is safe. We use a secure connection ( Secure transaction (https)) and once your transaction is completed, Loot does not keep a record of your credit card number. The only record Loot keeps is the authorisation number received from the bank. This is to ensure against the use of stolen cards.

## Email Alert

EmailAlert emails contain IDs that are unique to each user. Please do not divulge your password or forward EmailAlert emails onto others as they could access your personal details stored in MyLoot.

In addition to our safeguards your personal information is protected in the UK by the Data Protection Act. This provides that the information which we hold about you should be processed fairly and lawfully and should be accurate, relevant and not excessive. The information should, where necessary, be kept up to date and not retained for longer than is necessary. Please help us to keep your personal information accurate by updating your registration details on the website.

## More Information

For more information on the Data Protection Act and the Information Commissioner please see [http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk](http://www.informationcommissioner.gov.uk/)

## Changing or accessing your information

You can inspect your personal details at any time and modify them via MyLoot. Should you no longer wish to receive newsletters or services you have signed up for, or if you wish to review or receive copies of the personal information we hold about you, or have any other queries please email [registration@lootmail.com](mailto:registration@lootmail.com) including full details of your request.

We may charge a small administration fee in relation to fulfilling a request for access to personal information.

Back to [Terms & Conditions](http://www.loot.com/rs6/homepage.asp?action=q&t=/general/about_loot/company_information/terms_and_conditions)

|
